{"test_questions": [[{"question": "What type of join is needed when you wish to include rows that do not have matching values?", "opta": "Equi-join", "optb": "Natural join", "optc": "Outer join", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What type of join is needed when you wish to return rows that do have matching values?", "opta": "Equi-join", "optb": "Natural join", "optc": "Outer join", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is true concerning a procedure?", "opta": "You do not create them with SQL.", "optb": "They do not need to have a unique name.", "optc": "They include procedural and SQL statements.", "optd": "They are the same thing as a function.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A CASE SQL statement is which of the following?", "opta": "A way to establish an IF-THEN-ELSE in SQL.", "optb": "A way to establish a loop in SQL.", "optc": "A way to establish a data definition in SQL.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is true concerning routines and triggers?", "opta": "Both consist of procedural code.", "optb": "Both have to be called to operate.", "optc": "Both run automatically.", "optd": "Both are stored in the database.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is one of the basic approaches for joining tables?", "opta": "Subqueries", "optb": "Union Join", "optc": "Natural join", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is true concerning systems information in an RDBMS?", "opta": "RDBMS store database definition information in system-created tables.", "optb": "This information can be accessed using SQL.", "optc": "This information often cannot be updated by a user.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The following SQL is which type of join: SELECT CUSTOMER_T. CUSTOMER_ID, ORDER_T. CUSTOMER_ID, NAME, ORDER_ID FROM CUSTOMER_T,ORDER_T WHERE CUSTOMER_T. CUSTOMER_ID = ORDER_T. CUSTOMER_ID", "opta": "Equi-join", "optb": "Natural join", "optc": "Outer join", "optd": "Cartesian join", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Embedded SQL is which of the following?", "opta": "Hard-coded SQL statements in a program language such as Java.", "optb": "The process of making an application capable of generating specific SQL code on the fly.", "optc": "Hard-coded SQL statements in a procedure.", "optd": "Hard-coded SQL statements in a trigger.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A UNION query is which of the following?", "opta": "Combines the output from no more than two queries and must include the same number of columns.", "optb": "Combines the output from no more than two queries and does not include the same number of columns.", "optc": "Combines the output from multiple queries and must include the same number of columns.", "optd": "Combines the output from multiple queries and does not include the same number of columns.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is true concerning subqueries?", "opta": "Involves the use of an inner and outer query.", "optb": "Cannot return the same result as a query that is not a subquery.", "optc": "Does not start with the word SELECT.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is a correlated subquery?", "opta": "Uses the result of an inner query to determine the processing of an outer query.", "optb": "Uses the result of an outer query to determine the processing of an inner query.", "optc": "Uses the result of an inner query to determine the processing of an inner query.", "optd": "Uses the result of an outer query to determine the processing of an outer query.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "Correlated subquery references a column in the outer query and executes the subquery once for every row in the outer query while Uncorrelated subquery executes the subquery first and passes the value to the outer query."}, {"question": "How many tables may be included with a join?", "opta": "One", "optb": "Two", "optc": "Three", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The following SQL is which type of join: SELECT CUSTOMER_T. CUSTOMER_ID, ORDER_T. CUSTOMER_ID, NAME, ORDER_ID FROM CUSTOMER_T,ORDER_T ;", "opta": "Equi-join", "optb": "Natural join", "optc": "Outer join", "optd": "Cartesian join", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is true concerning triggers?", "opta": "You do not create them with SQL.", "optb": "They execute against only some applications that access a database.", "optc": "They have an event, condition, and action.", "optd": "They cannot cascade (cause another trigger to fire).", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}